Brother, can I talk to you?
Where is your wife?
You have a very hot clash with your wife.
It is true, man of God.
Very, very hot clash.
It is true.
In the world, we call it abomination.
Is this your wife?
Yes, man of God.
Prophecy Time
You are the wife.
Yes, man of God.
Why do you allow your appearance to deceive you?
When you look at the mirror, you look beautiful; you allowed that to deceive you.
You allowed your appearance to deceive you and you want to destroy your marriage.
Yes, man of God.
What you did is bad.
I hope you have confessed to him.
Yes, man of God.
I want to be part of this family.
Listen.
It is satan that wants to destroy your home; it is not her.
You know, I was saying something -
begin to reject any torture from the enemy of your soul.
It is the enemy of our souls that tortures us with depression.
"Ah, this man is... I'm light in complexion. I'm a beautiful woman..."
This is your wife.
What happened was to destroy this marriage.
Anything close to Jesus receives attack.
Thank you, man of God.
She has confessed to you, what else again?
It is a dirty thing.
When I was there, I just saw a very hot situation in the marriage.
Don’t listen to your people; listen to God.
Don’t listen to Mr T.B. Joshua, listen to Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You did this stupid thing on your street.
It is not a distance but on the street.
This is your wife; you cannot get any other woman.
This is your father.
If this man listens to God, he is no longer only your husband
but your father because he has discretion.
He can say, "I will not take what God says, this is shame..."
but he wants to listen to God.
Yes, man of God.
He is your father.
Yes, daddy.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Alex Tshiteta.
The woman beside me is my wife.
We are coming from Zambia.
Last week Sunday, the man of God located me and he prophesied into my life.
He asked me, "Where is your wife?"
I did not know where she was, so she came and the man of God said, "This is your wife".
I agreed, "Yes, she is my wife".
The man of God said, "What happened in your marriage was an attack from satan".
I agreed; it was an attack from satan.
We have not been together for 1 year and six months.
The man of God said, "This is your wife.
She has apologised for whatever she did - you have to forgive her".
The prophecy is true.
It all started way back, in 2016; we separated...
We were married when we were young, and I knew and understood her very well
I noticed that there were some things that began to change in her; the way she reacted and did her things.
I was expecting that she was seeing someone else.
Being an "IT personnel" I did not want to accuse her,
so I took it upon myself and said, "Let me find out what really is happening".
I downloaded a software on her phone that allowed me to have access
to everything happening on her phone,
whenever she was communicating, chatting - I was able to know.
As time went on, I began to realize that she was seeing someone for real.
Then I confronted her; she confirmed and said it was true.
I was furious and angry.
I decided and said, "If it is like this, you have to pack and go your way".
We separated - it is now almost 1 year and 6 months we have been apart.
Last week, when the man of God located us and prophesied into my life,
he told me it was an attack from satan.
He said that everything that is close to God receives attacks.
I began to understand that it was an attack for real.
After that we were prayed for and we were delivered and I begin to have the same affection I had,
some time ago when we were newly married.
After the deliverance and the prophecy from the man of God, my heart has been relieved;
I'm able to sit down with her and talk to her - we are now together as husband and wife.
That is not enough for Jesus Christ - put your hands together beautifully
for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ, who has restored this marriage to the glory of God.
You have said it all.
Right now, with your experience and what really happened, we believe you are in the best position
to advise all and sundry - what word of advice do you have to render?
My advice to everyone out there is that:
when you are exhausted in this life due to circumstances or challenges,
maybe in your marriage, business, or career,
you should not give up because your emotions may lead you astray
but God will lead you on the right path.
It is better for you to really find out what God is speaking over your situation.
Amen. You have heard it all.
Indeed, it is a wonderful piece of advice and it is all in tune with the Word of God.
When we make mistakes, as we all do, we should not run from God, but rather we should run to Him,
for an instant and immediate solution to all fundamental issues of life.
Without further ado, we want to hear from your wife.
My name is Mrs Mary Tshiteta.
The problem that brought us here: we have been separated for 1 year and 6 months.
We have been going to so many places looking for a solution, but none was found.
That's how I came to The SCOAN.
Last Sunday, during the service, the man of God located my husband.
He told him that there was a hot clash and abomination that happened in our marriage.
He asked my husband, "Where is your wife?"
That was when I came out.
I confirmed the prophecy to be true, because it all started with me.
We got married at an early stage.
We have 3 kids.
The spirit in me led me to start feeling like,
"Since I got married at an early stage, I don't know what is on the other side of life.
I don't know what is on the other side of the coin; a coin has 2 sides."
I didn't feel comfortable with myself.
So, I started going out to meet another man-friend, without my husband knowing or his consent.
After my husband found out, he confronted me and I confessed everything to him.
That's how he got upset.
He said, "If it is like this, you have to go back to your parents' house".
That's how I went back to my parents.
We have been separated for 1 year and six months.
That's how we came here and the man of God prophesied to us, prayed for us,
delivered and counselled us.
After the deliverance, the affection, the love that I had for my husband,
the love that we had when we were young is back, and we are able to relate together even better.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
We thank God Almighty for what He has done in your lives.
What do you have to say to your husband right now?
I would like to apologize to my husband, because I have hurt him so much.
I brought shame to him.
I was supposed to be his wife but I became his embarrassment.
I want to use this opportunity to apologize to him, to say that I am so sorry.
Mrs Mary Tshiteta & Husband
Prophecy Testimony
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Only Jesus Christ can justly do this.
We thank God Almighty for this wonderful restoration.
We believe the Lord has done it, and it shall remain permanent.
Finally, what word of advice do you have for all who are listening to you?
My word of advice to my fellow young ladies, women is that:
Do not be moved by what is happening in the world out there.
If you feel those emotions that lead you astray, it is better you run to God.
The Bible says he who finds a wife, finds a good thing.
So, let God lead us to be good thing, a blessing to our husbands and not a burden.
Let's run to God.
Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
It has been indeed a wonderful word of advice.
We thank the Lord Jesus Christ, who has used His able servant, Prophet T.B. Joshua to reconcile,
and bring this couple together once again and forever.
We pray as both of you go and make the Word of God the standard for your lives,
that this reconciliation and blessing will remain permanent.
And always have it at the back of your mind, that better is not good enough, the best is always yet to come.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
TT ROBERT BEGIER 13/11/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 16/11/2018